Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 2)
  - Resources Dept
    - Form Letters to Contributors and Foundations from 1972
      - 1972-1973 (Box 78, Folder 49)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 78)
    - Forrest, Winston, Correspondence and Memos, 3/3/1976-7/21/1980 (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Foundation News the Family Planning Field: Its Needs are Far from Met, 9/1974-10/1974 (Box 78, Folder 51)
    - Fund Raising, Correspondence, 12/1/1970-9/27/1972 (Box 78, Folder 52)
    - Fund Raising Kit (incomplete), 1974 (Box 78, Folder 53)
    - The Fund Raiser (Affiliate Newsletter), 5/1978 (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - Giving In America: Toward a Stronger Voluntary Sector. Report of the Commission on Private Philanthropy, 12/2/1975 (Box 78, Folder 55)
    - Grantsmanship Center Training Program Scholarships, 4/5/1978-2/6/1979 (Box 78, Folder 56)
    - Handbook from PP Solicitors, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 57)
    - IPPF/PPFA Formula Financial Arrangements, 3/10/1976-10/30/1978 (Box 78, Folder 58)
    - IPPF/PPFA 50/50 Formula, 10/22/1969-7/15/1970 (Box 78, Folder 59)
    - List of Planned Parenthood Contributors, Legal (Paul, Eve), 3/30/1979-9/11/1979 (Box 78, Folder 60)
    - List of Priority Project Proposals for Merrill Trust and Other Donors, 9/22/1970 (Box 78, Folder 61)
    - Mott "YAPP" Plan General, 1/6/1966-12/13/1966 (Box 78, Folder 62)
    - NY State Legislation, Solicitation of Charitable Organizations, 10/23/1975 (Box 78, Folder 63)
    - Nurses Training Proposal, Donor Requests, 9/21/1970 (Box 78, Folder 64)
    - Philanthropy 1965, Some Techniques and Areas of Interest, William Carpenter, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 65)
    - Other "Publicity Supported" Organizations, 1966-1970 (Box 78, Folder 66)
    - Pill Questions from Prospective Donors, 11/28/1977 (Box 78, Folder 67)
    - Population Resources Center, 1/23/1979 (Box 78, Folder 68)
    - Private Income Report, Major Donors, Special Donors, Direct Mail Etc., 8/1978 (Box 78, Folder 69)
    - Procedures Governing Sharing of Income and Donors between PPW and Affiliates, 2/1974-3/1974 (Box 78, Folder 70)
    - Projects For Funding, 1976? (Box 78, Folder 71)
    - Proposal for Presentation to Business Council, George Beach, 12/15/1970 (Box 78, Folder 72)
    - Proposal for Creation and Utilization of New Fund Raising Structure, circa 1970 (Box 78, Folder 73)
    - Proposal to Reg. Reps. for Special Gifts Fund Raising, 3/1975-4/1975 (Box 78, Folder 74)
    - Rating Bureaus Standards, Nonprofit Org., 1/7/1978 (Box 78, Folder 75)
    - Regulation of Charitable Solicitation, (Paul, Eve Director of Legal Services), 8/29/1978-4/26/1979 (Box 78, Folder 76)
    - Resources Policies, 3/1/1973 (Box 78, Folder 77)
    - Report on Special Projects, 9/22/1971 (Box 78, Folder 78)
    - Restricted Grants Campaign, 5/28/1970-12/9/1970 (Box 78, Folder 79)
    - Some Basic Questions and Answers About Campaigns, Contributors, Contributions, 2/27/1970 (Box 78, Folder 80)
    - Today's Challenge for Tomorrow's World, A Case Statement for PPFA Inc., 1977 (Box 78, Folder 81)
    - Trust Agreements, Samples, circa 1979 (Box 78, Folder 82)
    - Justice Fund, Advisory Council Mtg., 10/13/1977 (Box 78, Folder 83)
    - The Justice Fund, 7/10/1977-12/7/1979 (Box 78, Folder 84)
    - Justice Fund, Summary of Justice Fund Activity in the Field of Litigation, Legal, (Paul, Eve), 10/18/1978-2/28/1979 (Box 78, Folder 85)
    - Report on Justice Fund Activities, Novick, Lee, 10/24/1978 (Box 78, Folder 86)
    - Laurence, Deborah, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 87)
    - Robbins, John
      - Affiliate Turf Consideration and Problems, 5/16/1973-5/30/1974 (Box 78, Folder 88)
      - Appeals to 39 Rich Businessmen, 8/27/1973-10/12/1973 (Box 78, Folder 89)
      - Analysis and Reorganization of Dept., 8/22/1974-11/27/1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Appeals to Individuals, 11/22/1972-10/4/1974 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Candidates for Director of Resources, Correspondence, 10/3/1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Comparison Table for 1973-1972 Affiliate Revenue, 8/14/1974 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, General
        - 1974 (Box 79, Folder 5)
        - 1975 (Box 79)
      - Corporate Contributions, 6/18/1971-5/9/1974 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Draper World Population Fund, 1/27/1975-5/19/1975 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Donors List, 1/26/1974-3/15/1974 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Evaluation, Regional Fund Raising Consultants, 4/25/1974 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Foundations, 12/21/1973-6/28/1974 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Foundations' Population Fund (H.L.McIntyre)
        - 1974 (Box 79, Folder 11)
        - 1975 (Box 79)
      - Job Description, Dir. Resources Assoc. for Special Gifts, 8/7/1974-10/28/1974 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Oram, Harold Consultant from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 13)
        - 1975 (Box 79)
      - Phillip Lochner Consultant, 4/12/1973-1/16/1974 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - PPFA-WPEC Fund Raising, 1/8/1974-2/26/1974 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Report of the Center's Fund Raising, 4/1974 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Victor and Victor Bostrom Funds from 1974
        - 1971, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 17)
        - 1975 (Box 79)
      - Wise Study Estimating Savings Accruing from Family Planning, 4/12/1974-5/3/1974 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - International Convocation On the World Population Crisis, Final Report, 10/7/1974 (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - International Convocation on the World Population Crisis, Organizing Committee, 2/21/1974-3/8/1974 (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - World Population Year Convocation, Program Committee Questionnaire, 4/22/1974-5/20/1974 (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - World Population Year Convocation
        - 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 22)
        - 1975 (Box 79)
      - International Convocation of the World Population Crisis, General, 6/19/1974-6/20/1974 (Box 79, Folder 23)
      - International Convocation on the World Population Crisis Papers, Remarks, Speeches, Statements, 6/1974 (Box 79, Folder 24)
      - T.V. Fund Raising, 12/1974 (Box 79, Folder 25)
      - Why Private Funds are Needed, 8/12/1970 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Rodman, Jules
      - General Correspondence, 4/28/1970-12/15/1971 (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - List of Donors Who Skipped in 1970 and Assignments Made, 9/23/1971 (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - Memos, Mimeos, 7/6/1970-12/17/1971 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Speidel, Jess W.
      - Affiliate Turf Problems, 4/26/1973-10/31/1973 (Box 79, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1/11/1971-3/21/1974 (Box 79, Folder 31)
      - PPWP Chronological, 2/2/1973 (Box 79, Folder 32)
      - Memos, Mimeos, 1/2/1973 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - A Survey of the PP Movement Here and Abroad, Activities and Expenses, 7/1/1970-6/30/1971 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Resources, Solicitors' Handbook, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Tax Exemptions, 4/16/1970 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Wilson Bill: HR 10922 Charitable Resources Solicitation Requirement Bill, 8/2/1976 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Affiliates, Orientation for Executive Directors, 5/25/1961-6/25/1970 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - 1.610 Training Dept.
    - A Basic Cost System for a Training Program Manual, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Administrative Assistant/Secretary Workshop, 2/5/1974 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Depts. Applications, 3/19/1969 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 8/16/1968-10/30/1974 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Board Training, Policy Formation Seminar, 4/10/1974 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - CDF-PPWP Family Planning Seminar, 2/1/1972-4/5/1972 (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - Dallas, Texas Training Program, 1/6/1970-4/20/1970 (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - Dallas, Texas Training Program, 10/22/1968-12/31/1969 (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - Documents and Annual Work Plan, 10/1/1975 (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - Dept. of Labor, New Careers Contract N9-8922-99, 11/18/1968-3/30/1971 (Box 79, Folder 48-50)
    - DHEW Regional Offices, 12/1/1970 (Box 79, Folder 51)
    - The Employment and Training Opportunities Act of 1970 (S.3867) (H.R.18095), 1970 (Box 79, Folder 52)
    - Executive Director's Training, 9/30/1969-6/14/1971 (Box 79, Folder 53)
    - Fort Worth, Texas, Training Program, 9/24/1970 (Box 79, Folder 54)
    - General, Mimeos, 8/12/1969-10/39/1974 (Box 79, Folder 55)
    - A Handbook for the Evaluation of FP Training 1975 MDTP, 5/1975 (Box 79, Folder 56)
    - A Handbook for Evaluation of Family Planning Training, 11/1974 (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Job Description, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - New Careers Project, Stein, Francine S., 1/14/1969-6/10/1971 (Box 79, Folder 59)
    - New Careers, Misc. General, 11/8/1968 (Box 79, Folder 60)
    - National Family Planning Conference New York City, 10/14/1973-10/19/1973 (Box 79, Folder 61)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 6/30/1970-8/6/1973 (Box 79, Folder 62)
    - Survey Questionnaire for Training Project, 12/20/1973 (Box 79, Folder 63)
    - Project, Financial Management Requirements, Training Program, Family Planning Aides, 12/30/1968 (Box 79, Folder 64)
    - Interviewing: Family Planning Style Training Manual, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 65)
    - National Family Planning Management Institute
      - 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 66)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 79)
      - Executive Director's Training, 9/24/1971-12/22/1972 (Box 79, Folder 67)
      - Dialetics Inc. Person Power, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 68)
      - Advance Management Seminar, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 69)
      - Evaluation of Results, J.C. Robbins, 11/29/1973 (Box 79, Folder 70)
      - Help Inc. (Cornelia O'Connor), circa 1972 (Box 79, Folder 71)
      - Feedback Format, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 72)
      - General from 1973
        - 1974 (Box 79, Folder 73)
        - 1975 (Box 79)
      - First Annual Report, 4/1/1972-6/25/1973 (Box 79, Folder 74)
      - Human Resources Management Seminar, 10/7/1974 (Box 79, Folder 75)
      - Oberg "Charisma, Commitment and...," 1972 (Box 79, Folder 76)
      - "The Irish Coffee Case," circa 1974 (Box 79, Folder 77)
      - Policy Formation Seminar, 7/11/1974-7/18/1974 (Box 79, Folder 78)
      - Policy Formation Seminar, 8/10/1973-8/23/1973 (Box 79, Folder 79)
      - Phase One Workbook, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 80)
      - Phase One Workbook with Answer Keys, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - "PreConference" Notebook, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Phase Two with Case Studies, 1972? (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Programming and Budgeting Seminar, 8/6/1974 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Readings for Programming and Budgeting, 1974? (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Schedule, 6/12/1974 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Strategy Readings, circa 1972 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Workshop Program Design and Personnel Planning, 10/22/1975 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Training Seminars, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Advanced Management Seminar, Keller, Kansas City, 12/13/1976-6/15/1977 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Keller, Vaughn, Correspondence and Memos, 7/13/1972-10/20/1972 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - The Non-Profit Board of Directors, Keller, 2/22/1976-4/2/1976 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Keller, Vaughn, Reorganization of Board Committee Structure, 11/25/1975 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - "Solving Problems" by Vaughn Keller, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Vaughn Keller, Training For New Executive Directors, 10/31/1977-4/17/1978 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Vaughn Keller, Training (Orientation) for New Executive Directors, Evaluations, 2/13/1978-3/23/1978 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - National Family Planning Management Institute, Job Assessment Survey, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Vaughn Keller, PPFA Program, 12/2/1977 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - National Center for Family Planning Services, 11/20/1970-2/18/1972 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Newark, NJ Training Program, 10/23/1968-5/15/1970 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - New Orleans, LA Training Program, 1/2/1969-1/26/1971 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - North Carolina Area Training Program, 12/31/1969-2/25/1970 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Planning Conference SW Region, Dallas, Texas, 12/3/1971-12/27/1971 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Peace Corps' Office of Returned Volunteers, 5/28/1971 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Physician Training in IUD, 11/30/1970 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Projected Dept. of Training Projects and Cost Estimates for FY1972, 12/22/1970 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Rural Training Session, Pinehill, KY, CDG, Field Dept., 5/24/1971-9/14/1971 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - New Careers Staff Conference, Airlie House, Warrenton, VA, 7/28/1969-8/28/1969 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Suffolk, NY, Training Program, 10/23/1968-11/10/1970 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Training Staff Functions, 11/12/1970 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Train the Trainers Program, 8/9/1972-5/30/1973 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Tri-County Training Project, 11/5/1969 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Unmet Needs SMSA, 5/29/1969 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Urban Training Session, Norwalk, CT, CDF, Field Dept, Training Dept., 6/7/1971-9/14/1971 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Vaughn Keller, The Seminar In Strategic Planning, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - 1.610 PROPOSALS
      - DHEW Proposals, Correspondence, 5/21/1971-5/22/1971 (Box 80, Folder 36)
      - Executive Directors' Training Proposal Texas, 1970 (empty folder) (Box 80, Folder 37)
      - Paraprofessional Manpower Development Training Project, 1972-1973 (Box 80, Folder 38)
      - Proposals, 5/15/1970 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Training For Family Planning Services: A Proposal for a National Program, circa 1972 (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Nurses Training Proposal, 10/27/1970-1/27/1971 (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - 1.610 REPORTS
      - Manpower Development Project, Financial Report, 8/16/1976 (Box 80, Folder 42)
      - Cybern Training Dept, Planned Parenthood Training Center Evaluation Report, 3/15/1969-3/20/1969 (Box 80, Folder 43)
      - Report, OEO Sponsored Paraprofessional Manpower Development and Training Project, 6/11/1971-7/16/1971 (Box 80, Folder 44)
      - Report of the Director, Charles Patterson, on Development of Training Program, circa 1969 (Box 80, Folder 45)
      - Report of Training Dept. to Annual Meeting, 10/13/1970-10/19/1970 (Box 80, Folder 46)
      - Statistical Report on Training Delivered, 5/24/1971 (Box 80, Folder 47)
    - Continuing Education
      - Miriam Manisoff, 5/15/1970-10/1/1970 (Box 80, Folder 48)
      - Continuing Education "Capsules," 1/1970-4/1970 (Box 80, Folder 49)
      - Indiana Conference August 1964, 12/5/1963-7/28/1966 (Box 80, Folder 50)
      - California Seminar, 3/25/1963-4/6/1967 (Box 80, Folder 51)
      - Professional, 11/14/1966-3/21/1972 (Box 80, Folder 52)
      - General Correspondence, 10/30/1962-5/16/1969 (Box 80, Folder 53)
      - Lists, Events, Misc., 3/25/1963-2/17/1969 (Box 80, Folder 54)
    - National Training Laboratories, 12/29/1954-7/12/1962 (Box 80, Folder 55)
    - Professional Education
      - M. Manisoff
        - 1970-1974 (Box 80, Folder 56)
        - 1977 (Box 80)
      - Correspondence, 1/20/1969-12/30/1969 (Box 80, Folder 57)
      - 1/10/1967-11/25/1968 (Box 80, Folder 58)
      - M. Manisoff, Family Planning, Nurse Specialist Training Program
        - 1971-1973 (Box 80, Folder 59)
        - 1974-1979 (Box 80)
      - Review and Analysis of PP Training Centers, 5/8/1968 (Box 80, Folder 60)
    - Health and Welfare Programs, Elliot, Robin, Correspondence, 1/9/1970-1/26/1970 (Box 80, Folder 61)
    - New Careers Project Directors, Hazzard, V., 2/5/1970-4/10/1970 (Box 80, Folder 62)
    - Parker, David W., Correspondence, 7/1/1971-10/17/1972 (Box 80, Folder 63)
    - Paraprofessional Training, F.S. Stein, 1/5/1970-3/22/1971 (Box 80, Folder 64)
    - John Palmer Smith
      - Correspondence, 12/24/1969-5/12/1971 (Box 80, Folder 65)
      - Hospitals, 6/9/1970-1/20/1971 (Box 80, Folder 66)
      - Systema, Inc., Correspondence, 4/9/1971-5/18/1971 (Box 80, Folder 67)
  - Africa, FPIA
    - Activity Reports, Perez, Edward L., 3/7/1973-5/9/1973 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 12/8/1971-4/24/1973 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Botswana, 7/6/1972-5/16/1973 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Burundi, 2/7/1972-5/15/1973 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Cameroon, 11/28/1972-5/18/1973 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Egypt, 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 6-10)
    - Ethiopia from 1971
      - 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 81)
    - Ethiopia, 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 12-14)
    - Ghana
      - Field Report, Leonard Robinson, 11/20/1973 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - 1/18/1972-5/3/1974 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - 1973 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - 1975 (Box 81)
      - 1979 (Box 81, Folder 18-20)
    - Jordan
      - 8/24/1973-9/6/1973 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - 1978 (Box 81, Folder 22-23)
    - Kenya
      - 1971-1974 (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - 1977 (Box 81)
      - 01 Project, 02 from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 25)
        - 1975 (Box 81)
      - 8/30/1973-9/27/1973 (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 27-29)
      - Communications Workshop, 3/19/1973-7/11/1973 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Lambia [sic?], 3/14/1973 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Lesotho
      - 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - 1976 (Box 81)
      - Proposals
        - 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 33)
        - 1975 (Box 81)
    - Liberia
      - 12/7/1971-6/29/1972 (Box 81, Folder 34)
      - 1/3/1979 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Malawi, 12/28/1971-11/21/1972 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Projects, Misc. Correspondence, 3/13/1973 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Nigeria
      - 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 38-39)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 40-46)
      - Proposal, Correspondence, 12/8/1972-2/12/1973 (Box 81, Folder 47)
    - Republic of South Africa, 3/6/1973 (Box 81, Folder 48)
    - Rwanda, 1/26/1973-3/7/1973 (Box 81, Folder 49)
    - Sierra Leone, 1/13/1972-2/14/1972 (Box 81, Folder 50)
    - Sierra Leone, 8/30/1978 (Box 81, Folder 51)
    - Sudan, 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 52-54)
    - Tanzania
      - 10/8/1971-5/17/1973 (Box 81, Folder 55)
      - 1979 (Box 81, Folder 56)
      - Grant, 3/27/1973 (Box 81, Folder 57)
    - Uganda, 10/8/1971-4/9/1973 (Box 81, Folder 58)
    - West African Population Conference, Abidjan, Ivory Coast, 5/31/1973 (Box 81, Folder 59)
    - Zaire
      - 1979 (Box 81, Folder 60-61)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 62)
      - 1975 (Box 81)
    - Zambia, 10/8/1971-5/18/1973 (Box 81, Folder 63)
    - Participants, African Regional IE&C Workshop, 6/15/1973 (Box 81, Folder 64)
    - African Regional IE&C Workshop, Evaluation, 1973? (Box 81, Folder 65)
  - Asia, FPIA
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 8/2/1971-3/11/1974 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Bangladesh
      - 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - 1977 (Box 82)
      - Project Proposal
        - 1973 (Box 82, Folder 3)
        - 1974 (Box 82, Folder 4)
        - 1975 (Box 82)
      - circa 1975, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 5-19)
    - Hong Kong, 2/15/1972-8/31/1973 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - India
      - 1/12/1972-10/16/1973 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Demonstration Pill Project, 1/23/1973-5/10/1974 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Indonesia
      - 1971-1973 (Box 82, Folder 23-24)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 25-28)
      - Muhammadiyah FP Program, Outer Islands, 1/26/1979 (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - 1979 (Box 82, Folder 30-31)
    - Korea
      - 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 32-34)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 82, Folder 35-40)
    - Nepal
      - 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 41-42)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 43-47)
    - Oman, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 48)
    - Pakistan, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 49-53)
    - Philippines
      - Correspondence
        - 1971-1974 (Box 82, Folder 54)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - Projects, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 55)
      - 1978 (Box 82, Folder 56)
      - Jescomea
        - 1973 (Box 82, Folder 57)
        - 1975 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 58-59)
      - Iglesia N. Cristo, 12/16/1975 (Box 82, Folder 60)
      - 1979 (Box 82, Folder 61-63)
    - Taiwan
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82, Folder 64)
      - Maternity and Child Health Demonstration Project, 4/20/1973 (Box 82, Folder 65)
      - Projects, 8/24/1973-8/29/1973 (Box 82, Folder 66)
    - Thailand
      - 12/22/1971-4/11/1974 (Box 82, Folder 67)
      - Coordinating Conference for Directors of Christian Hospitals, Bangkok, 12/7/1973-12/20/1973 (Box 82, Folder 68)
      - Communications Workshop, 3/19/1973-4/18/1973 (Box 82, Folder 69)
      - Projects, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 70-71)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 72-78)
  - FPIA (alphabetically by country)
    - Chinese People's National Committee, 2/1/1980-3/18/1980 (Box 82, Folder 79)
    - Costa Rica
      - 1971-1974 (Box 82, Folder 80)
      - 1976 (Box 82, Folder 81)
      - 1973 (Box 82, Folder 82)
      - circa 1975-1979 (Box 82, Folder 83-86)
    - Dominican Republic, 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 87-88)
    - El Salvador, 1/26/1978-1/27/1978 (Box 82, Folder 89)
    - England, Correspondence, 8/20/1971-11/28/1973 (Box 82, Folder 90)
    - Fiji, 4/10/1973 (Box 82, Folder 91)
    - Guatemala, 8/15/1978 (Box 82, Folder 92)
    - Haiti
      - 1973 (Box 82, Folder 93-94)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 95)
      - Ad Hoc Coordinating Committee on Family Planning Assistance to Haiti, 12/29/1971 (Box 82, Folder 96)
    - Honduras, 10/3/1978-10/16/1978 (Box 82, Folder 97)
    - Maldives
      - 1/11/1979-1/19/1979 (Box 82, Folder 98)
      - Action Familiale, 5/10/1973-10/18/1973 (Box 82, Folder 99)
      - 10/17/1979-10/19/1979 (Box 82, Folder 100)
    - Mexico
      - 1977-1979 (Box 82, Folder 101-112)
    - New Guinea, 4/11/1974 (Box 82, Folder 113)
    - Papua, New Guinea, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 114-116)
    - Sierra Leone, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
    - Sri Lanka, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 3-5)
    - Tonga Family Planning Association, 4/10/1973 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Turkey
      - Correspondence
        - 1972 (Box 82, Folder 7)
        - 1975 (Box 82)
      - circa 1975-1979 (Box 82, Folder 8-11)
  - FPIA, South America
    - South America, 4/11/1973-7/12/1974 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Bolivia, 6/20-25/1979 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Brazil, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 14-16)
    - Columbia, 7/15/1976 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Ecuador
      - 1974 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - 1976 (Box 83)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 19-20)
    - Peru
      - 1972-1974 (Box 83, Folder 21-22)
      - 1975, 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 23-33)
  - FPIA
    - International Clearing House Adolescent Fertility, 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 34-35)
    - International FP Perspectives/Digest, 10/24/1978-10/25/1978 (Box 83, Folder 36)
    - Workshop for East Asia Grantees, 3/15/1978-3/20/1978 (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Workshop In a Community Approach to FP, 6/7/1978-6/8/1978 (Box 83, Folder 38)
    - Reducing the Risk: International Year of the Child, 3/22/1979 (Box 83, Folder 39)
    - Expenditures, All Regions, 11/7/1977 (Box 83, Folder 40)
    - Abortion-Related Activities, 6/27/1974-12/16/1974 (Box 83, Folder 41)
    - Budgets, 10/20/1977-9/25/1978 (Box 83, Folder 42)
  - FPIA, Agency for International Development
    - AID from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 83, Folder 43)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - Contract, Legal (Paul, Eve), 9/7/1978-10/10/1978 (Box 83, Folder 44)
    - Audit from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 83, Folder 45)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 83)
    - Country Priorities, 3/14/1974 (Box 83, Folder 46)
    - Office of Contract Management, FJ Mocado, 9/15/1975-4/11/1978 (Box 83, Folder 47)
    - Family Planning Services Division
      - 1972-1974 (Box 83, Folder 48)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 83)
    - Grant Aid/pha-G-1131, 1975-1978 (Box 83, Folder 49-51)
    - Grant Aid/csd- 3289
      - Only copy with original signatures, 6/30/1971 (Box 83, Folder 52)
      - Amendments
        - 1972-1974 (Box 83, Folder 53)
        - 1975 (Box 83)
      - Implementation Plan for Improvements in the Program Operation, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 54)
        - 1974 (Box 83, Folder 55)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 83)
        - 1971-1974 (Box 83, Folder 56-58)